mevio.com 2013-06-09

# Mevio - Privacy Policy

#### Effective as of February 17, 2011.

## Introduction

This privacy policy discloses the privacy practices of Mevio, Inc.. and its subsidiaries (collectively, "Mevio," "we", "our" or "us"), which own and operate various sites on the World Wide Web, including without limitation mevio.com, MusicAlley.com, Mevio.Co.Uk, MevioCoupons.com, and PodcastAlley.com, (collectively, the "Mevio Websites"). This privacy policy covers the operation of all Mevio Websites. 

Mevio provides professional and semi-professional episodic entertainment produced by Mevio, other networks, producers and production companies. Mevio Websites also include user generated content that is produced by independent producers. All of this content (the "Content") can be downloaded, viewed, or streamed onto your computer or portable multimedia player for your enjoyment. Your access to and use of the Mevio Websites, the Content, and all the services provided via the Mevio Websites (collectively, the "Mevio Services") are subject to Mevio's Terms of Use and all applicable laws. 

This privacy policy describes how Mevio collects, uses, and shares information about you that it obtains in connection with providing Mevio Services to you. 

We value your comments about our privacy statement and invite you to e-mail us with suggestions and concerns. 

For the purposes of the Data Protection Act 1998 (the 'Act'), the data controller is MEVIO UK LTD. 

## What information is collected

In order to enhance your user experience and improve the Mevio Services, Mevio collects information about you from two sources: (i) information you affirmatively give to us; and (ii) information automatically collected when you visit any of the Mevio Websites or use any Mevio Services. Third parties may also collect your information in connection with your use of Mevio Services. 

When you sign up for Mevio Services, we will ask you to provide certain information about yourself such as your name, email address and postal address. You can view all of the information collected during the registration process by visiting the registration page. You may modify or remove any of your personal information at any time by logging into your account and accessing features that will allow you to edit your profile and account Information. After you provide such information and set up your account, we may ask you to provide additional information about yourself on an optional basis. We may ask you for certain financial information, including credit card account data or other payment method data, to process payments for some of our premium services. From time to time, Mevio may sponsor promotions, sweepstakes and/or contests. In connection with such events, Mevio may ask you to provide personal information including name, email address or home address or to answer questions in order to participate. You may provide to Mevio email addresses of your friends in order to invite them to Mevio Services by sending invitation emails through our automated invitation system. Mevio may collect any communication it has with you via any means, including e-mail, telephone, and letters. 

By choosing to provide any information to us, you are giving Mevio permission to use and store such information consistent with this privacy policy. 

### Information we collect automatically

In addition, Mevio automatically collects information about your interactions with the Mevio Websites and Mevio Services. For example, Mevio may automatically collect information about your use of the Content on the Mevio Website. Mevio may also log information from your computer and browser, such as your IP address, profile information, aggregate user data, browser type, software and hardware attributes, pages you request, and cookie information. By using the Mevio Services, you are giving Mevio permission to use and store such information consistent with this privacy policy. 

You may refuse to accept cookies by activating the setting on your browser which allows you to refuse the setting of cookies. However, if you select this setting you may be unable to access certain parts of our site. Unless you have adjusted your browser setting so that it will refuse cookies, our system will issue cookies when you log on to our site. 

### Information collected by third parties

Mevio may use services that collect data remotely by using "pixel tags," "web beacons," "clear GIFs," or similar technologies. Such technologies can recognize certain types of information on your web browser, check whether you have viewed a particular web page or email message, and determine, among other things, the time and date on which you viewed them and the IP address of the computer from which you viewed them. 

Mevio Services may include advertisements from third parties, often with the ability to click through to websites or properties run by third parties. Mevio is not responsible for the privacy practices of such advertisers. Once you leave the Mevio Services by clicking on an advertisement, you should carefully review the privacy policy of the advertiser to determine how it handles information it separately collects from you 

Some of the advertisements that appear in connection with the Mevio Services may be delivered to you by third party Internet advertising companies (also called "ad networks" or "network advertisers"). These companies may use cookies, web beacons, and other technologies to collect non-personal information about your visits to Mevio Websites. Mevio does not have access to or control over cookies, web beacons or other technologies that they may use. The information practices of these advertising companies are governed by their own privacy policies and are not covered by this privacy policy. Some of these advertising companies may be members of the Network Advertising Initiative ("NAI"), a cooperative of online marketing companies that offers a centralized tool for opting out of behavioral advertising delivered by each of its member companies. If you would like to obtain more information about the NAI and make choices about their use of your information, please [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp). 

Mevio Services may be linked to or provided through third party websites. Mevio is not responsible for the privacy policies and/or practices on such third party websites. When linking or accessing such websites, you should carefully review the privacy policy of such third party to determine how it handles information it separately collects from you. 

## How information is used

Mevio uses the information it collects from you to deliver Mevio Services to you and continuously enhance your user experience. Generally speaking, we use the collected information to communicate with you, fulfill your requests, customize the Content and advertising, improve our products and services, protect our and your rights, and comply with laws and regulations. 

We may use your personal information to send you promotional information and updates regarding Mevio and its products and services. You may choose not to receive such information and opt-out of such future communications by [clicking here](http://www.mevio.com/mc/account_settings/). All such communications sent to you will also contain instructions for opting-out. 

We may use the email addresses that you provide in connection with inviting potential new users to communicate with such potential new users regarding your invitation. Recipients of such invitations may contact us to request the removal of their information from our database. 

The information that we collect about you may be used to display targeted advertisements and promotional offers to you. Except as expressly provided in this privacy policy, Mevio does not provide any personal information to the third party advertisers or offerors when you interact with or view a targeted advertisement or promotional offer. 

The information that we collect from you may be used in aggregate form in various ways to optimize and improve Mevio Services. While such information may be based on information about you, it will not identify you personally. We may use such information for the following purposes: website management, administration and security, promotional activities, research and analysis, and advertising. 

## With whom information is shared

### Public Information

Mevio may share as it sees fit information that you voluntarily make public, including information that you post on any blogs, message boards, chat rooms or other similar forums, whether or not such forums are owned by Mevio. Since such public information can be accessed by the public and used by any member of the public, such use by third parties is beyond the control of Mevio. 

### Personal Information

If we have your consent, Mevio may share your personal information that it collects with advertisers, business partners, and other third parties that are not affiliated with Mevio. Note that if you sign up for service from one of our partnership program affiliates, we may ask for your consent to share with such third party partner certain of your personal information. While Mevio is not responsible for the acts of such partners, we encourage all of our partners to adopt privacy policies that protect against the disclosure of personal information to third persons. 

We may disclose your personal information to any member of our group, which means our subsidiaries, our ultimate holding company and its subsidiaries, as defined in section 1159 of the UK Companies Act 2006. 

Mevio may disclose your personal information without asking for your consent in order to protect the legal rights of Mevio or its affiliates, and each of their respective investors, directors, officers, employees, agents, and suppliers; to protect the safety and security of users of the Mevio Services or to enforce our Terms of Use; to protect against fraud or for risk management purposes; or to comply with or respond to the law or legal process or a request for cooperation by a government entity, whether or not legally required. If you notify us that you believe your legal rights have been violated by Mevio or another user of the Mevio Services, we may provide the information that you provide to us to others to the extent that we believe it is necessary to evaluate and respond to your complaint. For instance, if you submit a notice of copyright infringement to us, we may send a copy to the person or entity who uploaded, stored, or transmitted the material addressed by the communication. 

Also, in order to provide goods or services that you have requested or to complete a transaction at your request, Mevio may share your personal information with its third party service providers, including companies that assist with payment processing, business analytics, data processing, account management, advertising, and other services. We require these companies to agree that they will only use personal information about you that they have obtained from us to provide us with specific services that we have requested and not for any other purpose. 

### Non-Personally Identifiable Information and Aggregate Data

Mevio may share with third parties your non-personally identifiable information and related aggregated data. For example, (i) Mevio may share IP addresses of its users to provide anonymous aggregated data to advertisers about the volume of use on the Mevio Services and the specific Mevio Services in which users are most interested; and (ii) Mevio may share information about its users with advertisers so they can measure the effectiveness of advertisements viewed through the Mevio Services. Because this form of data does not identify particular users, these third parties will not be able to contact you based solely on this data. 

### Change of Control

If Mevio sells all or part of its business, or makes a sale or transfer of assets, or is otherwise involved in a merger or business transfer, or in the unlikely event of bankruptcy, Mevio may transfer your personally identifiable information and non-personally identifiable information to one or more third parties as part of such transaction. 

## How you can control the information we collect, use and share

You have the choice about whether to disclose your personally identifiable information or other information about yourself to Mevio. Regardless of your choices with respect to promotional communications and updates regarding content, Mevio may send you administrative messages, service announcements, terms and conditions of your account, or other similar communications, without offering you the opportunity to opt out of receiving them. 

You can change your privacy settings at any time by [clicking here](http://www.mevio.com/mc/account_settings/). You may delete your Mevio account, in accordance with our [Terms of Use](http://www.mevio.com/terms/?view=tou "Terms of Use"). Please note that, if you cancel your account, Mevio may retain some information about you but will remove your profile from the Mevio Website. 

## How information is protected

Your Mevio accounts are secured by member-created passwords and reasonable precautions are taken to ensure that your account information is kept private. You are responsible for keeping your passwords confidential. We ask you not to share your password with anyone. Mevio uses reasonable measures to protect your information stored within our databases, and we restrict access to such information to those employees who need access to perform their job functions, such as our customer service personnel and technical staff. Any payment transactions will be encrypted using SSL technology. Despite these efforts, please note that we cannot ensure or guarantee the security of your information. Unauthorized entry or use, hardware or software failure, and other factors may compromise the security of your information at any time. 

## Users from outside the United States

Mevio and its Mevio Services are based in the U.S., and our offices are headquartered in the U.S. Please be aware that information you provide to us or we obtain as a result of your use of the Mevio Services may be processed and transferred to the U.S. and be subject to U.S. law. This information may also be processed by staff working for us or for one of our suppliers in the U.S. The privacy and data protection laws in the U.S. may not be equivalent to such laws in your country of residence. By using our website, participating in any of the Mevio Services, or by providing us with your information, you consent to this collection, transfer, storage, and processing of information to and in the U.S. Mevio will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that you data is treated securely in accordance with this privacy policy. 

## Access to information

The Act gives you the right to access information held about you. Your right of access can be exercised in accordance with the Act. Any access request may be subject to a reasonable fee to meet our costs in providing you with details of the information we hold about you. 

## Changes to this privacy policy

From time to time, we may make changes to this privacy policy. In order to ensure that you are familiar with our most updated policies and practices, you should check the effective date indicated above of this privacy policy each time you use the Mevio Services. If we make any changes, we will notify you of such changes by posting the updated privacy policy on the Mevio Websites. We may also send you an email alerting you of such changes. You will be bound by any such changes to the policy when you use the Mevio Services after those changes have been posted. If we make material revisions concern practices where we have represented that we will obtain your consent to use or disclose your personal information, we will obtain your consent before taking any action inconsistent with those representations. 

## Contacting Mevio

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of the Mevio Website and Mevio Services, or your dealings with Mevio, please contact us at: [privacy@mevio.com](mailto:privacy@mevio.com "send email to privacy@mevio.com")
